{
    "subject": "resource/Jan_Delay",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/Germany",
    "human_readable": "Jan Delay was born in Germany.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9064464569091797,
            "question": "Is Jan Delay German?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8094053864479065,
            "question": "Where was Jan Delay born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7637869119644165,
            "question": "When was Jan Delay born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6550614237785339,
            "question": "What nationality is Jan Delay?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.636248767375946,
            "question": "In what country did Jan Delay originate from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4412008821964264,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Jan Delay's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4210606515407562,
            "question": "What is Jan Delay known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4196772575378418,
            "question": "Is there any famous landmark near Jan Delay's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3044084906578064,
            "question": "Where does Jan Delay live now?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1461746096611023,
            "question": "What kind of music does Jan Delay make?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jan Delay was born in Germany.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7467_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where does Jan Delay live now?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7467_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any famous landmark near Jan Delay's birthplace?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7467_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Jan Delay known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7467_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7467_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7467_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7467_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7467_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7467_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7467_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7467_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7467_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7467_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7467_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that all documents mention Jan Delay's country of origin as Germany, and his birth year and date are consistently mentioned as 1976 and August 25, respectively. Therefore, the statement \"Jan Delay was born in Germany\" is supported by the information in the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Jan Delay was born on 25 August 1976 in Hamburg, Germany. This supports the statement that Jan Delay was born in Germany."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}